Contact

Balagtas Batangas City 09298289932 (Mobile) Ricolittawa030620@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rico-littawa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js
Cloud Computing
Responsive Web Design

Certifications

AWS Educate Introduction to Cloud 101

Fortinet Network Security Expert Level 1: Certified Associate

Rico Littawa

Passionate Web Developer | Front-End & Back-End Development | HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP

Batangas, Calabarzon, Philippines

Summary

I am familiar with using javascript, html, and css. I worked as a frontend developer during my prior internship. We used the node.js, vue.js, and quasar framework technologies for Pixel8. My internship only dealt with front-end development, but I have experience with the back-end as well because I utilized PHP to create our college capstone project. At my workplace, I also acquired the skills necessary to use axios to fetch data from an API. I also have QA experience because I was given that role during my last weeks of the internship. My responsibility as a quality assurance officer is to determine whether or not other interns' tasks were successful or unsuccessful. If they didn't succeed, I use gitlab to provide feedback on their code.

Experience

Pixel8 Academy (Training Center) 4 months

Frontend Developer February 2023 - May 2023 (4 months)

Brgy Cruzada, Legazpi City, Albay, Philippines

I was tasked with working as a frontend developer throughout my internship at pixel8. Using the instructions provided, we are building web pages. I created websites using axios, node js, vue js, and the quasar framework. We've been tasked with creating one of the pages for our organization's project management system, together with my colleagues.

Quality Assurance Intern February 2023 - May 2023 (4 months)

Brgy Cruzada, Legazpi City, Albay, Philippines

On my final day as an intern, I was assigned the duty of doing quality assurance checks on other interns' work. I am the one who examines their codes. I also provide them with guidance on how to write cleaner code. When

providing feedback I use gitlab to create an issue and notify them about their remarks.

Education

Batangas State University

BS Information Technology, Business Analytics · (August 2019 - May 2023)